Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Two gunman have been
shot dead after they opened
fire in a shopping
center in England.
- As many as 80.000 residents of
the city have fled their homes
to escape the shooting at.
- .. Government forces in the
southern Philippines have
launched an offensive
against rebels
as fighting escalates in this
part of Asia's largest
Catholic country.
- A national day of mourning
in the Philippines.
after 44 police commandos were
killed in the line of duty when
an anti-terror
operation went wrong.
- 200 heavily armed separatists
from the National Liberation
Front attacked the city.
- .. The officers from the
Police
Special Action Force were
killed during an operation
to capture one of
the most wanted terrorists.
♪ ♪
Philippine authorities now say
the toll in yesterday's hotel
bombing has risen to 146
dead and 231 wounded.
It is the most devastating
terrorist attack in Asia.
in 10 years.
And the worst ever. in Manila.
While no organization has taken
responsibility for the blast.
Western intelligence sources
have identified chemical traces
that are the hallmark of
the infamous arms-dealer.
Aarmir Barkawi
International security experts
say that the Barkawi family is
now instigating violence in
remote capitals to foster
instability. and thus fuel
massive arms sales
around the globe.
♪ ♪
(Raza) There he is.
(Kamran) - Kamran.
- Raza.
(Raza) Did Philippine
intelligence track you?
OK.
(Kamran) Father.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
We need to discuss
Major General Rahman .
It's your sister's wedding.
(Kamran) I'm sorry.
This can't wait.
I think your ISI
officer was compromised.
Kamran. all Pakistani
intelligence officers
are compromised.
One of our Afghani
friends discovered a German
BND agent in his circle.
And?
That particular general won't be
very useful to us anymore.
He's been eliminated.
Thought you might want to know.
Don't forget his family.
Vengeance must always be
profound and absolute.
♪ ♪
(Amal) So am I.
I'm very happy.
♪ ♪
(JSOC Officer) Pentagon just
received target confirmation
from MI6 ground asset.
(JSOC Officer) You're
clear to execute.
[explosion]
♪ ♪
Hell of a presidential
race. sir.
- Every day the
same damn joke.
- Seriously?
What the hell did
they make you out of?
Bourbon and poor choices.
- You pick a name yet?
(Banning) We were thinking
Benjamin if it was a boy.
- Really?
- Hell no!
If it's a girl. maybe.
- Voight. you wanna
run over him for me?
Believe me.
sir. we've tried.
(Banning) Baby?
Babe.
What?
(Leah) Little problem
in the nursery.
All right. so six
cameras. right?
One. two. three.
four. five. six.
- What. is that too much?
- Yeah. maybe.
Yeah. it's too much.
I thought that.
They're baby gifts
from the guys.
I'll take them down.
(Leah) All we need
is one baby monitor.
One baby
monitor. right. OK...
...and a Kevlar mattress.
- And a Kevlar mattress.
- Come here.
- Unhand me.
- Never.
And guess who just
got the next week off?
Don't toy
with me. young man.
'cause there will
be consequences.
No. no. we're
finishing this nursery.
I can't believe it's
taken me this long.
- Paint samples.
- What?
- Yeah. I gotta show you these
amazing new paint samples.
- Can I get
a shower first?
- God. yes!
♪ ♪
(Aide) Sir. Speaker of
the House is waiting.
And the Senate Majority Leader
would like five of your time.
I'll take him first.
When is Trumbull getting back?
The Vice President has three
more days of vacation and
insinuated considerable violence
if he heard my
voice before then.
Yeah. never get
between that man and a fish.
(Another Aide) Sir. I got
your son on video chat.
(Asher) Excellent. He had his
first date last night.
(Advisor) Mr President.
you need to take this. sir.
(Aide) Sir. Speaker
of the House?
(Advisor) You need
to take this now. sir.
(Asher) This is the president.
OK.
Thank you.
(Reporter) Sources confirmed
that Prime Minister James Wilson
has died while sleeping in his
residence at 10 Downing Street.
He is believed to have
suffered a heart attack.
possibly from complications
after a surgical procedure to
repair his knee a day earlier.
An autopsy has been scheduled
within the next 48 hours to
determine the actual
cause of death.
(Leah) It's the White House.
It's OK.
My mom can come over.
[helicopter]
[chimes of Big Ben]
(Home Secretary Kenter) What
we are proposing is that the
funeral takes place
this Thursday. the 9th.
4pm at St Paul's.
The confirmed attendees
are all world leaders.
with the lone exception
of the Russian president.
Well. no love lost there.
Our Royal Family will attend a
private service at St James's
Palace. the morning of. with 28
other heads of state
from all over the globe.
As per foreign royals.
Prince Albert of Monaco.
Queen Rania of Jordan.
Saudi Prince Muqrin.
Yes. it's a
logistical nightmare.
But let's make sure this
runs without a hitch.
Questions?
And what special
requests have the Yank circus
demanded so far?
Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders
part of the retinue possibly?
That's a request
I could live with.
I'm partial to
the Kardashians myself.
as apparently is Her Majesty.
Nineteen special
requests from twelve
different countries.
We've denied all of them.
Any issues of special concern
with our current assessments?
We all know about
the 350 or so British nationals
who've travelled back and forth
to Syria in the past year.
as we've seen before in
Iraq and Afghanistan.
Of rising concern is the
handful we believe to be
former military.
(Lancaster) - Is any
of this actionable?
- No.
Very well.
Then we will see off our dear
friend James with dignity.
Give him the
ceremony he deserves.
(Jacobs) Sir?
Are you ready for us?
- Yeah. come on in.
Take a seat.
What are you guys so damn
nervous about?
The Brits are
world class.
We all know their reputation.
But. still. these
are the trips I hate.
Last minute. Out
of the country.
No time to plan.
Are you sure I can't
talk you out of this?
(Asher) Lynne. it's
a state funeral.
It's our oldest. strongest ally.
I spent half the night on the
line with our advance team.
Metropolitan police will secure
the perimeter of the funeral at
St Paul's Cathedral.
Air Force One will land
at Stansted Airport.
On the ground it's all Mike.
(Banning) Touchdown.
Then a 12-minute chopper
ride to Somerset House.
From there we take an
armoured-vehicle escort down
Fleet Street to the cathedral.
(Asher) You don't seem thrilled.
(Jacobs) Well. the British
have their hands full.
(Banning) It's a clusterfuck...
sir.
Well. 40 different
countries
with 40 different
security teams.
Minimal flexibility
on approach routes.
funeral seating. egress.
- Can we make it work?
- Mike?
I always do. sir.
Good.
I know it's not great
timing for you. but...
- It's what I do.
- Thank you. sir.
There's my man.
Mr Vice President.
How was your vacation. sir?
Son. do you have any idea the
joy a man feels pulling
a 70-pound king mackerel out of
the waters around Jekyll Island?
- No. sir. I don't.
- That makes two of us.
And I'll have to wait until
next year to find out.
But thanks for asking.
(Leah) Oh. yeah.
that's in the Sinai.
- It's beautiful.
- There you go.
That's incredible.
I love these things.
They all are...
Don't worry about a
thing. We'll be fine.
Doris. can
we have a minute?
Sure.
You meant Leah. Right.
- Very funny. Doris.
And she tells me not to worry.
- It's only three days.
- Yeah.
- And I'm not due for two weeks.
(Banning) The walking away
ain't quite so easy this time.
(Leah) Hey. I got this.
You go and you do what you have
to do and we will be right here
when you get back. OK?
You. say bye-bye to Daddy.
Bye-bye. Daddy.
Bell tolls.
Yeah.
I love you.
You better.
Behave.
♪ ♪
Here you go.
Thank you.
You've been
hiding lately.
You busy nesting?
Something like that.
Your idea of nesting
being bullet-proofing the walls
of the nursery?
Now. that is
actually a great idea.
(Jacobs) Yes.
I'll do it.
Well. that only
took two weeks.
It's no small
thing being a godmother.
I mean. I didn't take
your asking lightly.
I know. You think you
can handle it?
Well. I'm
competent. brilliant.
stunningly beautiful and
really fucking honoured.
Really honoured.
Thank you. Lynne.
♪ ♪
Big day ahead?
- Correction. Mega day. Morning.
Thank you.
- Just your signature
here. please.
Thank you. sir.
(Chief Hazard)
Gentlemen. ladies.
Today I need your
undivided best.
The most important people in
the world are in our care.
so muck in and get it right.
(Intel Officer) Always. Chief.
(Chief Hazard) Good
morning. London.
♪ ♪
(Banning) Southpaw has landed.
- Agent Banning. John
Lancaster from 5.
- Hey. John.
- Bit early. aren't you?
Nope. We're moving
up our schedule.
- I see.
The fewer people know
the President's exact movements.
the better.
- Why wasn't I told?
- Nobody was.
That's how you
keep it a surprise.
(Lancaster) Well.
thanks for the help.
[clock chimes]
(Newsreader) With security
at unprecedented levels in
anticipation of the funeral. set
to begin just an hour from now.
this isn't just a gathering
of the world's most powerful
leaders. it is the most
protected event on earth.
(Officer) Rooftops in position.
All units in position.
(Pilot) Marine One. Two and
Three on final approach
to Somerset House.
(Air Traffic Controller) Marine
One cleared for landing.
♪ ♪
[sirens]
[footsteps marching in time]
(Bruckner) It's OK.
Thank you.
(Soldier) Stand at ease!
[sirens]
Yeah. I understand.
Yeah. I promise.
Everything is
going to be fine.
Important
matters of state?
That was
daughter number two.
She didn't pass
her driving test.
Guess whose
fault it is?
♪ ♪
How Much Longer ?
We Are Almost There Sir.
I'm sorry. but as expected...
...there are heavy
security measures.
[Chimes of Big Ben]
I can't believe
we're doing this ...
A private tour Of
Westminster Abbey ...
... just for you.
I only turn 30 once.
It's time Mr. President.
The cars are ready.
But. not too ready...
Wait ten minutes?
At least.
[sirens]
(Agent) Southpaw has
arrived at destination.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Bugs the shit out of me.
(Jacobs) Thank you.
- Sir.
- Thank you. Mike.
(Clarkson) Thank you
very much. Lynne.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Good to see you.
(Clarkson) Benjamin.
thank you for coming.
We're grateful
you could make it.
- I'm sorry.
You know. the funny thing is.
James always hated funerals.
Yeah. don't we all?
[explosion]
[gunfire]
Get down!
(Jacobs) Mike!
Mike!
(Banning) Move!
Let's get inside!
Shit!
(Jacobs) All right.
back to the car!
- OK. OK. OK.
(Banning) Grenade!
Down!
Go.
Beast is compromised.
Fuck. They're
not real cops.
Two at the front!
Gulf One to CAT team.
Support on me now.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Stay with me. We'll
get you out of here.
Down!
- Shit.
- Goddammit. Mike.
[sirens]
[explosion]
[tortured squeal of bending
metal. screaming]
[explosions]
[massive explosion]
(Female Intel Officer)
Oh. Jesus.
There's been a massive
attack at the cathedral.
- Chelsea Bridge has
collapsed.
- So has Westminster Abbey.
- Get me SO15 Counter Terror.
- Yes. sir.
- Where's emergency response?
- On their way. sir.
[sirens]
Voight. where the
fuck are you?
(Voight) Almost there.
(Banning) Move! Go! Go!
(Voight) You OK. sir?
Keep your head down.
(Banning) Get
inside! Get inside!
- Bronson! Bronson!
- Mike! Mike!
- Let's go!
- Mike!
- Go. go! Let's get to
the chopper.
♪ ♪
(Kamran) Dean Court.
black Land Rover.
(Asher) I don't believe it.
They overran everything.
(Banning) Not everything.
Looking for hard extract.
Marine One. for Southpaw.
Fuck. Comms are down.
All right. here we go.
Get down!
- Voight.
- Yo.
(Banning) Let him
get next to us.
- Copy that.
- Hold him. Hold him. Now!
Voight. hard brake now!
Drive!
(Voight) Come on!
(Banning) Down! Get down!
(Jacobs) Voight!
- Voight!
(Asher) Keep
pressure on the wound.
- Voight.
- Voight. Voight.
- He's dead. Lynne.
- Oh. God.
(Banning) Get down. sir.
(Jacobs) - Jacobs.
take the wheel.
- Got it!
- Get in!
- Got it.
(Asher) Mike. on your left!
(Jacobs) Get him!
Not really where
you wanna be right now.
(Terrorist) Fuck you!
- Fuck me?
Fuck you.
♪ ♪
We're almost there. sir.
(Agent) Come on. let's go.
(Banning) Go. sir. go!
(News Reader) Five world
leaders are confirmed dead.
along with hundreds
of innocent civilians.
in an attack that has decimated
most of the known landmarks in
the British capital.
♪ ♪
(Sultan) Clarkson
and Asher are alive.
All the rest are dead.
(Barkawi) And I thought it
was too much to hope for.
We just changed the world.
Plan B. Sultan.
Fate has smiled on us.
♪ ♪
(Sultan) Lights out. London.
[Explosion]
(Chief Hazard) The
generators will kick in.
(Clarkson) Ladies and
gentlemen. good evening.
We've asked the residents of
London to stay indoors for their
own safekeeping while the
situation remains fluid.
Let there be no doubt that every
relevant police authority and
counter-terrorism unit is
actively at work regaining
control of our streets.
and within hours...
(Doris) Call Mike.
- ...we will secure this city
and those responsible will be
swiftly brought to justice.
Jesus. it's
not connecting.
(Trumbull) How bad is it?
- It's pretty goddamn bad. sir.
All lines of communication
have been compromised.
Both civilian
and military.
- Shit.
- We've tasked satellites
and drones to get eyes on.
but so far nothing.
- Sentinel
Drone is on station.
We have visuals incoming.
They're coming up.
(Trumbull) Oh. my God.
- Nearest quick
reaction force?
- Sicily. Two hours out.
(Trumbull) Spin them up.
And get a line to Downing Street
and to Box Emergency Command.
(Clegg) Yes. sir.
(Monroe) Satellite is up.
Marine One is airborne.
(Mason) - Southpaw is evac'ing.
- Yes!
(Pilot) Marine One with Southpaw
on board en route to Stansted.
Prepare Air Force One
for urgent departure.
Copy.
(Ground Control) Copy.
Air Force One prepped
and ready to go.
- It was a trap.
- That's an understatement.
Holy shit.
It's one thing to plan
for this. another to live it.
- All right.
well. we're good now.
- It'll be OK.
- Yeah.
We'll be on secure ground
in ten minutes. OK?
There was
no chatter on this. None.
(Asher) Something
of this magnitude.
it took years to
plan. and we had days.
- It's a fucking
blood bath.
How did they do
this. Mike?
They only have
to get it right once.
Today they got it right
way more than that.
Fuck.
(Marine Three Pilot)
Mayday. mayday. mayday!
(Co Pilot) Marine Three is down.
(Asher) Oh. no.
(Banning) Rooftop.
three o'clock!
You see them?
(Pilot) Marine Two. two
shooters at three o'clock.
(Marine 2 Pilot) Copy that.
(Banning) - We're being pinged.
- Stingers.
(Co Pilot) Deploying flares.
(Banning) OK. stinger down.
(Co Pilot) - Stinger
at three o'clock.
- Climb. climb.
(Marine 2 Pilot) - Marine One
out of flares.
- Marine Two out of flares.
(Pilot) - Marine Two.
prepare for sacrifice.
- Copy.
(Co Pilot) Marine Two is down.
Missile lock on.
Mr President.
we're going to take a hit.
Brace for impact.
(Mason) Oh. no.
(Banning) Sir.
Sir. are you good?
You OK?
Sit up.
Can you move?
Yeah?
OK. sir.
You with me?
- Yeah.
Lynne. Lynne!
No.
- My God. Oh. my God.
(Banning) Lynne?
Help me stop
the bleeding.
- Ben. Ben. Ben.
Get out of the chopper.
Ben. get out of the chopper.
This thing could
blow at any second.
Go.
Hey. Hey.
I never thought
you would outlive me.
Me neither.
(Jacobs) Oh. shit.
Do me a favour?
Stay alive.
You gotta see your kid.
Make those fuckers pay.
(Banning) I will.
Box Command. this is Gulf One.
Do you copy?
Fuck!
Fuck. Looks like we're walking.
Mr President. those better
be comfortable shoes.
(Mason) Sir. I think you're
gonna wanna take a look at this.
I'll put it up.
To our friends in the west
whose idea of war
is a remote dusty location
thousands of miles from the
comfort zone of your shopping
malls. who send your poor to be
blown to bits in our land or.
better yet. murder our families
remotely from the sky.
Your time is over.
We're bringing the war to you.
Make no mistake. this is the day
when your world changes forever.
Jesus.
- This is all over
social media too.
Everybody in the
world has seen this.
Aamir Barkawi.
(Mcmillan) Number
six on the ten list.
(Trumbull) This man is
responsible for more deaths
than the plague.
Sells arms to every
failed state in the world.
He has a vast array
of connections.
Terrorists. mercenaries.
corporations.
(Clegg) Mr Vice
President. it's Barkawi.
Put him through.
I thought you might
take my call.
You understand if I
made it difficult to track.
You have me at
somewhat of a loss.
I thought you would have learned
a lesson by now about crawling
out of your hole.
I never lifted
a finger against you.
You armed
those who have.
I sold triggers.
Mr Trumbull. just like you.
What do you want?
Your president.
You can end this right now.
Just hand him over.
That's not going
to happen.
Then every death from
this moment forward
will be on your head.
(Trumbull) Barkawi sells arms
through dummy companies.
some of them probably in London.
Find a connection to him.
He's probably been
planning this for years.
Everybody makes a mistake.
We have to find it before
he finds the president.
Let's get to it.
(Banning) - Mike.
he's a policeman.
- Yeah?
Not exactly standard
police issue.
Really?
(Asher) Oh. my God.
I've never seen a
man suffocate before.
I didn't have a knife.
He's got more ammunition
than the entire US army.
How could they pull
something like this off?
There's gotta be
somebody on the inside.
(Banning) Yeah. looks like it.
These ain't your typical
spray-and-pray hillbillies.
These guys are pros.
- We should go for the embassy.
(Banning) No. they'll
be expecting that.
There's an MI6 safe
house near here.
I have a contact there.
(Banning) We go there. we wait
it out and we get an extraction.
- Do you trust them?
- Yeah.
The fact is. every single one
of these guys is a terrorist
asshole until proven otherwise.
The only person you trust
right now is me. OK?
Come on. let's go.
(Banning) We gotta
get underground.
(Asher) These guys
are everywhere.
(Banning) Let's go.
Stay here. I'll be back.
- OK.
♪ ♪
(Voice on radio) Raza.
Raza.
(Banning) Here.
Or we can do this the
really fucking hard way.
(Kamran) Raza.
Answer me. brother.
(Banning) OK.
Raza's not feeling too
well at the moment.
He's a little bit fucked up.
Yo. what's this dickhead's name?
(Kamran) This is Kamran.
Who is this?
(Banning) Hey. Kamran.
My name's Mike Banning.
You are the
one with the president.
- Bingo.
So why don't you boys pack up
your shit and head back
to Fuckheadistan or wherever
it is you're from?
(Kamran) You should have
let us kill him quickly.
because now we're going to kill
him slowly and stream it live
for the whole world to see.
Can you hear me. Mr President?
- Tell him.
- Yeah. he can hear you.
Here's something I
want you to hear first.
That's the sound of
your brother dying.
Yeah. not much of
a talker. that one.
but I'll bet you one
of your men will.
I'll see you soon. Kamran.
- Was that
really necessary?
- No.
(Trumbull) The Brits
are compromised.
Police for sure.
Who do you trust?
We can also assume all
communications are compromised.
Anything that isn't secured
could get into the
wrong hands. sir.
And Banning
would know that too.
So how could he even
reach out for help?
(Monroe) There. Freeze that.
Sir. is Banning left-handed?
No. he's right-handed.
(Monroe) OK. well. the President
doesn't move without a drone or
a satellite over his head.
Banning knows that.
(McMillan) It's his left hand.
Southpaw. six.
Shorthand for MI6 .
Look for any
MI6 location in that area.
- Yes. sir.
- All right. Banning.
♪ ♪
- You OK?
- Hell. yeah.
Made out of bourbon
and bad choices. huh?
(Banning) Sit down.
Take deep breaths.
How many you think died?
I don't know. A lot.
All those
innocent people.
Dead. because of me.
No. not because of
you. Because of them.
They're trying to kill you. sir.
And they've killed all these
people just to make everyone
else a little more afraid.
Well. fuck that and fuck them.
Mike. you don't let
them take me.
- I'm not going to.
- Let me finish.
If it comes to it. if
it's going to happen...
- Sir...
- Mike.
If it comes to it. I
want you to kill me.
That's an order.
I will not be executed for
propaganda as my son and the
American people see
me on fucking YouTube
for the rest of their lives.
(Banning) OK.
(Chief Hazard) Vice President
Trumbull. it's an honour. sir.
Chief Inspector.
(Lancaster) I'm afraid
our news isn't promising.
Our dearly departed Prime
Minister James Wilson
was assassinated.
Poison in his anesthesia and
his doctor's body found dumped
about an hour ago.
(Trumbull) State funeral.
Must-attend event
for Western leaders.
Each one a target.
Goddamn.
And we walked right into it.
(Chief Hazard) And all
dead. bar your man and ours.
What's happening on
the ground?
The terrorists have
killed 19 first
responders with another
30 unaccounted for.
(Med Department Head)
They're impersonating us.
Our people are walking
right into ambushes.
(General) Say the
word. we go in.
But make no mistake. we
risk turning London
into another Fallujah.
That's the last
thing we need.
the President in the
middle of an urban battle.
(Chief Hazard) Or the
citizens of London.
You're just as likely to take
out half the Metropolitan police
force unless you can tell
me how you can tell the
difference between the good
guys and the bad guys.
We're gonna have to stand
down our emergency services.
Surrender London?
- He's right.
Take out all
legitimate personnel.
Anyone that remains
is a terrorist.
Look. the sooner we end this.
the more chance there is of
stopping London becoming a
complete war zone.
Well. how do we get the
word out to our people?
Air-raid system.
We sound that.
people know to stay
secure in their place.
Then we let the
military sweep in.
go door to door if necessary
and clear these bastards out.
[air raid sirens]
♪ ♪
[door buzzer]
(Male voice on
intercom) Good evening.
(Banning) Is Auntie in?
[buzzer]
Put that away.
- Are you who I
think you are?
(Asher) Unfortunately.
(Banning) Thanks.
What a pleasure this is.
two handsome men
visiting me on
such a lovely evening.
- Long time. Jax.
- Yeah. not long enough.
Mr President.
Sir. Jacquelin.
Mi6's finest.
Don't fuck with her.
(Asher) Hello.
(Jacquelin) The phones are down.
That said. it did allow
us to pick up this.
(Trumbull) Mr
President. Banning.
I hope this finds you well.
Mike. we got your message and
I'm sure you don't know who you
can trust. and all prior
authentications may be
compromised. so I
offer you this...
Do you have any idea the joy
a man experiences pulling a
70-pound king mackerel...
(Banning) Out of the waters
around Jekyll Island?
It's him.
(Trumbull) A Delta team has
been clandestinely inserted.
By now they should be en
route to your position.
They'll take you to the US
embassy where an armoured convoy
stands by to get you out of
SAM range and
onto a military jet.
(Asher) Thank God.
Let's get us out of here.
(Banning) All right. so
who's behind all this?
(Jacquelin) Aamir Barkawi.
(Asher) Barkawi
provides armaments.
He's a fucking criminal.
Shielded by governments.
Mike. there was a drone strike
to get him two years ago.
authorised by the G8.
so we took a shot.
He survived.
We didn't know his
family was there.
His daughter was killed.
Well. he certainly
got his revenge.
Civilians?
Well. they're not being
targeted specifically. but...
- Collateral damage?
- Yeah. quite a lot. I'm afraid.
It's government targeted.
No official support
from any country.
It's Barkawi's show.
But he didn't have any problems
finding recruits. did he?
It's the United Nations
of every-fucking-body
that hates us.
(Banning) Who's on the inside?
There's gotta be somebody.
Yeah. you're right.
They've infiltrated
our CCTV system.
And that can't be done
outside the network.
(Banniong) Yeah. but who?
- I don't know.
(Asher) Mike. if you hadn't
moved our schedule up...
(Banning) Here you go.
sir. Get this down you.
- Thanks.
(Banning) I don't know about
you. but I'm thirsty as fuck.
(Asher) Yeah.
(Banning) How you doing?
(Asher) I was just
thinking about my son.
He sends me these
jokes every day.
It's kind of our...
I don't know. our thing. or...
A little off colour.
His mother wouldn't
approve. but...
I tell you something. Mike.
these little messages I get from
him every day. they
mean everything.
You'll see.
Most important thing. never
criticise. always encourage.
You just want them
to be passionate.
That's what I
always tell my son.
Find something you care
about and care deeply.
That and the golden rule.
Treat others as you'd
like to be treated.
- That's it?
- Yeah. basically.
- What about
all the other stuff?
You know. sleeping. eating.
electrical outlets. diapers.
stairs and...
- That stuff
takes care of itself.
- Really?
- No. You'll figure it out.
I think your
dates have arrived.
(Banning) When did Trumbull
leave that message?
6:13.
(Banning) 32 minutes.
No way they got here that fast.
- Is there a zoom-in?
- Yeah.
(Banning) They're not sweating.
- What?
- That gear weighs 40 pounds.
They just stalked all the way
from outside the wire
and not a drop of sweat?
(Jacquelin) It's gotta be them.
Now they're
going round the back.
This doesn't look like
a rescue formation.
(Asher) Please don't tell me
that's not our Delta team.
They've intercepted
Trumbull's message.
(Banning) Jax.
where's the armoury?
(Jacquelin) Go.
(Banning) - Are you not coming?
- They'll have this
place surrounded.
They catch us in the
open. we're done.
But they're not looking for you.
Go. Find the mole.
Right. The wheels are in
the garage downstairs.
(Banning) All right. point
this end towards the bad guy.
(Asher) This is not good. Mike.
Stay in here. Stay down.
And if anybody but me opens that
door. you empty that into them.
What if you don't come back?
- You're fucked.
- Mike.
- Don't jinx me.
That was inspiring.
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
[cocks gun]
[gasping]
[gunshot]
I was wondering when you were
gonna come out of the closet.
That's not funny.
We're almost
out of this. sir.
I have another mile
in me. Mike.
OK. let's go.
- God bless MI6.
- I'll drive. you shoot.
♪ ♪
What the fuck are
you doing here?
- We have a mole.
- I know.
Well. any ideas?
Someone high up with
access to everything. routes.
security protocols...
emergency services.
Jacquelin.
what brings you here?
(Kamran) Do we have
the embassy covered?
(Sultan) Affirmative. brother.
Double the men. I want every
single man on that perimeter.
Shit.
The car's bullet-proof.
not politician-proof.
Hey. I'm the President
of the United States.
I haven't driven a car in
six years. What do you want?
Fuck. Take a left.
[squealing tires]
- Where we going. Mike?
- Embassy.
Embassy? Sure
they're expecting that.
They are. but we
are shit out of options.
Take a right.
Mr Vice President. you wanted
us to find Barkawi's mistake.
Take a look at this.
(Jacquelin) Of the 119 known
Barkawi front companies he's
used in the past...
(Monroe) 28 have been located
in the UK. 11 in London proper.
Well. that's not news.
But it's a baseline.
Now. every entity he's ever
used in the past followed a
very rough communication
pattern except...
(Trumbull) No known
communication in or out ever.
Well. that's
under construction.
No one lives or works there.
That's why this is
particularly interesting.
I had my NSA analyst take
a peek at the power usage.
(Monroe) Through the roof
for the last three weeks.
Pretty odd. considering
nobody lives or works there.
Central London.
Right under our bloody noses.
Tell SAS that we're
gonna make a house call.
Right.
It doesn't feel right.
Slow.
Left.
OK. stop.
This don't
look good. Mike.
There's no way
to dress this up. sir.
It isn't good.
Could be worse.
We could be walking.
Attaboy.
Don't stop for anyone.
[squealing tires]
[gunshots]
Fuck!
- Are we clear?
- Yeah.
[laughs]
- We fucking made it.
- We did. We did it.
(Banning) Mike!
(Asher) Mike!
[gunshot]
Where is he?
- Stop!
- Where is he?
Where the fuck is he?
Where is he?
Where'd they take him?
Broadwick
and Lexington.
Stop. He's done. Leave him.
Come on. Back off.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
You've gotta be Banning.
Will Davies. Captain 22. SAS.
Trumbull sent us.
Code Jekyll Island.
(Banning) President Asher
has just been taken.
and these assholes intend
to publicly execute him.
(SAS Lt.) We know. At 8pm
it's all over the internet.
We'll take care of it.
Move up.
Hey. hey. wait.
Look. we can't let you
come with us. mate.
How many times have you
saved this man's ass?
Now. I'm gonna go get him
and you can either kill me
or you can come with me.
but it ain't gonna
go any other way.
After you.
(Man) CCTV's back up.
What did you do?
Disabled the
authorisation code that shut
down the CCTV systems.
They've been
watching us using our own
surveillance systems.
Wait.
What authorisation code?
♪ ♪
You should be thankful.
How many men get to experience
their death witnessed
by billions live?
You are going to
go down in history.
I'm not the only one who's
gonna die today. Kamran.
Box Command.
Banning.
Mike Banning?
Chief Inspector Hazard. Scotland
Yard. Hold your position.
Our military will be on your
location in 20 minutes.
No. sir. The President's
gonna be dead in ten.
You don't understand.
We have NSA imagery
of where you're going.
It's their base of operations.
There are nearly a hundred
terrorists in there.
Yeah? Well. they should
have brought more men.
All right.
Things are gonna get sporty.
- Just watch your balls.
- Will do.
RPG!
Two o'clock clear!
Move up!
[loud scream]
OK. fuck that.
They're dug in like
ticks on a dog's arse.
We can't storm that building
with a force this small.
Yeah. They'd kill the
President the second we tried.
- Yeah.
- All right. call Box Command.
Make sure the utilities here
are isolated and switched on.
You sound like a
man with a plan.
- See the generator?
- Yeah.
- Let's poke out their eyes.
- Yeah. Generator. 12 o'clock.
- Fuck.
- What happened?
Power supply was just cut.
Get the emergency
generators up. Come on!
Mike.
(SAS Lt.)This is what we've got.
This is a three-storey building.
The entrance point is here.
There are two stairwells.
one here and one here.
We believe the President's
being held in this
room on the second floor.
Hold your position.
I need you to hit this building
with everything you got.
- You got it.
- Keep them busy.
I'll sneak in solo.
Take that.
Do not touch that
button until I tell you.
- Are you fucking crazy?
- Yeah. Wish me luck.
Don't shoot me.
♪ ♪
They are almost here.
Why don't you just kill him now?
No. The whole
world has to see this.
[gunfire]
You hear that. Kamran?
That's the sound
of inevitability.
I'm going to kill you live.
but that doesn't mean you
can't suffer privately first.
[coughing]
Look at me!
I held my sister as
she died in my arms.
We're all monsters.
Mr President.
I won't justify your
insanity to make you feel
better about yourself.
(Terrorist) Shoot him!
♪ ♪
(Sultan) Almost.
Power is back. We're waiting
for the internet connection.
Come on. come on.
Technology. Only as good as the
dumb shits who are using it.
- How long?
- Seconds.
- We're live now.
- OK.
Say hello to the
world. Mr President.
(Kamran) Any last
words. Mr President?
I do solemnly swear that
I will faithfully execute the
office of the President
of the United States...
Son of a bitch.
...United States...
...and will to the best
of my ability preserve.
protect and defend...
(Trumbull) Oh. my God.
I'm not watching this.
[gunshot]
[clicks empty]
You know what
you guys don't get?
We're not a fucking building.
We're not a fucking flag.
We're not just one man.
Assholes like you have been
trying to kill us for a long
fucking time.
But you know what?
A thousand years from now...
...we'll still fucking be here.
Mike. grenade!
What took you so long?
Sorry. I had a
couple of errands to run.
Shit. Does this fucker ever die?
All right. we've gotta go.
You good?
Let's get the
hell out of here.
[voices]
Go. go!
Go! Go. go.
go. go. go. go!
Ah!!
Mike. come on!
Dammit. I'm out.
I'm out too.
(Banning) Come in!
Davies.
We're trapped!
I repeat. we are trapped.
Blow it.
Are you insane?
I can't blow it yet.
You're not out.
We're not gonna
get out unless you do!
Just trust me!
Now. goddammit!
Go. go. go!
Banning?
Banning. do you copy?
Has anyone found
any sign of them?
(Soldier 1) Nothing. Over.
(Soldier 2) Negative.
OK. well. stay sharp.
Keep looking.
Box Command.
No sign of the President yet.
Box Command. we've found them.
[coughing]
The President's alive.
[cheering]
Yeah! Yes!
♪ ♪
Did I ever tell you?
I fucking hate funerals.
[laughs]
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Sir. I got you.
Mr President.
Banning.
That all they got?
Kind of looks like it.
Lieutenant.
this could be the
missing link to Barkawi.
I'll get it to Box
Command right away.
Next time I tell you
to blow it. just blow it.
Good job. Lieutenant.
You too. Banning.
Safe journey home.
If that's possible for you.
(Jacquelin) Next time you wanna
leave town after betraying your
country. how's about
you steal a car to take
you to your getaway vehicle?
Preferably one without a GPS.
'cause that just takes
all the fun out of it.
You forgot to delete
your access logs.
Your authorisation code's
there. bright as day.
The security cameras
show you logging on.
Just get on the floor.
Do I have to tell you this
is the most dangerous time
since the Great War?
They're cutting budgets while
the barbarians are at the gate.
The system's failing us. Jax.
It's broken.
You know it as well as I do.
Things have to change.
So you thought you'd
teach us all a lesson?
That and 20 million euros.
Come with me. Jax.
Get on the fucking floor.
John.
John. get on the floor.
Get on the floor. John.
Get on the fucking floor!
[gunshot]
(Man) Sir?
Kamran?
Mr Barkawi?
I thought you'd take my call.
You think this war. this
war that you started.
you think it's over?
I'll dedicate my
life to your death.
This war will not end.
Maybe you should
look out your window.
(Soldier) Clear to proceed.
Ground asset confirms target
clear of civilian presence.
(Anchor) Two weeks after the
devastating attacks on the
British capital. a new
government has been installed
and the city has
begun to rebuild.
In the words of Prime
Minister Clarkson.
'London may have fallen.
but it has always endured
and will rise again.'
(Leah) So Daddy's gonna be
taking some more time off.
Isn't that cool?
Yeah. maybe it's the new me.
Or maybe the President insisted.
Yeah.
[cries]
He says he reckons
I've earned a few days off.
thanks to you. little one.
[cries]
Yeah.
Yeah. it's OK. baby.
It's OK.
Yeah. it's OK.
I wonder what you're gonna
be passionate about. Lynne.
Yeah.
(Trumbull) Our hearts go
out to the people of London
and to our friends
around the world.
Far too many people
died for no good reason.
There are those who will say
that this would never have
happened if we would
just mind our own business.
Nothing could be
farther from the truth.
Frankly we live in a dangerous
world and we have few good
options. But the worst
option is to do nothing.
And finally we owe it to our
children and to their children
to engage in the world.
God bless you all and God bless
the United States of America.
(Anchor) That was
Vice President Trumbull live--
♪ ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org